vionicshoes.com 2018-09-25

# Privacy Policy

## Vionicshoes.com and Vionicbeach.com Privacy Policy effective February 28, 2014.

## Information We Collect

When you visit our website we may collect certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information may include Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. If you register or purchase products on our website, we collect information such as first and last name, email address, mailing address and billing information.

## Cookies

We may collect information through cookies. A cookie is a small data file that is placed on the hard drive of your computer when you visit a website. Through the use of cookies, we can display items added to your shopping cart from your previous session or make it easier for you to access your account information.

## Reviews, Comments, Communications and Other Content

Visitors may post reviews, comments, photos, and other content; send e-cards and other communications; and submit suggestions, ideas, comments, questions, or other information, so long as the content is not illegal, obscene, threatening, defamatory, invasive of privacy, infringing of intellectual property rights, or otherwise injurious to third parties or objectionable and does not consist of or contain software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings, or any form of "spam." You may not use a false e-mail address, impersonate any person or entity, or otherwise mislead as to the origin of a card or other content. We reserve the right (but not the obligation) to remove or edit such content. If you do post content or submit material, and unless we indicate otherwise, you grant us a nonexclusive, royalty-free, perpetual, irrevocable, and fully sublicensable right to use, reproduce, modify, adapt, publish, translate, create derivative works from, distribute, and display such content throughout the world in any media. You grant us and sublicensees the right to use the name that you submit in connection with such content, if they choose. You represent and warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the rights to the content that you post; that the content is accurate; that use of the content you supply does not violate this policy and will not cause injury to any person or entity; and that you will indemnify us for all claims resulting from content you supply. We have the right but not the obligation to monitor and edit or remove any activity or content. We take no responsibility and assume no liability for any content posted by you or any third party.

## How We Use Information We Collect

The information we collect is used to improve your experience when visiting our website. We also use the information to process purchase transactions, respond to your questions or comments and to contact consumers for marketing purposes.

We may disclose your information when requested in connection with a court order, legal process, or other judicial, administrative or investigative proceeding. Additionally, we may share personal information in connection with the sale or transfer of our business or assets.

## Information Shared with Third Parties

We may employ third party companies or individuals to process personal information on our behalf and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Examples include hosting or operating our website, sending email communications, marketing and data analysis.

We use third party marketing networks to place advertisements on other websites on our behalf. These third party marketing networks may place cookies or other code to compile data about consumers as they move from website to website. 

California law entitles residents to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties for those entities’ direct marketing purposes. We do not share, sell or provide any personal information to third parties for their own direct marketing purposes.

## Do Not Track

California Business and Professions Code Section 22575 (as amended January 1, 2014) provides that California Residents are entitled to know how websites respond to “Do Not Track” browser settings. We do not currently alter our practices when we receive Do Not Track signals. For more information about Do Not Track, [click here](https://leginfo.legislature.ca.gov/faces/billNavClient.xhtml?bill_id=201320140AB370).

## Children Under Age 13

Our website is intended for general consumers and we do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personal information without parental consent, we will delete such information.

## Links

For your convenience, our website may contain links to outside websites. We are not responsible for the web practices of those sites, and we expressly disclaim liability and responsibility for those links. Please review the respective privacy policies and terms of use provided on those sites if you have any questions about their web practices, which we have neither reviewed nor endorsed.

## Corrections and Updates

If you have registered for an account on our website and would like to make a correction or change to your account, you can do so by logging in to your account. You may also email us to request any corrections or updates at [info@vionicshoes.com](mailto:info@vionicshoes.com).

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we make any material changes to our privacy policy we will post the updated privacy policy on our website.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at:

Vionic Group, LLC  
4040 Civic Center Drive, Suite 430  
San Rafael, CA 94903  
Phone (415) 492-2190  
Email: [info@vionicshoes.com](mailto:info@vionicshoes.com)
